It's a secret mission!
Gizli görev!
Alright!
Tamamdır!
That'll be our decisive battle!
Bu büyük bir savaş olacak!
The battle will take place...
Savaş...
on an island called Onigashima...
Onigashima adındaki...
where Kaido and his Beast Pirates have made their base!
Kaido ve Canavar Korsanlarının adasında gerçekleşecek!
An island?!
Ada mı?
You mean we have to cross the sea within Wano?
Wano'da bile denizi geçmek zorunda mıyız?
That's right!
Doğru!
With the island practically visible from the coast, larger sailing vessels aren't required for the journey.
Ada kıyıdan gözüküyor zaten, oraya gitmek için koca gemilere ihtiyacımız yok.
However, we'll still need a boat...
Onigashima'ya baskın yapmak için...
if we are to raid Onigashima.
yine de bir gemiye ihtiyacımız olacak.
Well, we can worry about boats later.
Gemiyi sonra düşünürüz.
When are we doing this?
Savaşı ne zaman yapacağız?
The battle will be on the day of the Fire Festival.
Ateş Festivali gününde yapmalıyız.
The Fire Festival is a grand festival for the people of the capital.
Ateş Festivali başkent halkı için büyük bir festivaldir.
Kaido is considered a guardian deity of this country,
Kaido'nun ülkeyi koruyan bir tanrı olduğuna inanılıyor.
and on that day, Orochi will lead the Shogun's procession to Onigashima to pay tribute to him.
Ve o gün Orochi, tanrının huzuruna çıkmak için şogun alayı'nın başında Onigashima'ya gidecek.
But all that is merely pretense!
Ama bu sadece bir bahane!
In reality, they'll be holding a banquet for the officials and the Beast Pirates.
Asıl olacak olan şey, yetkililerin ve Canavar Korsanları'nın ziyafet vermesi!
I see...
Anlıyorum.
So we'll beat the hell out of those partying, drunken fools
Yani parti yaparlarken sarhoş olmuş o aptalları dövüp...
and take out their leaders!
liderlerinin kafasını keseceğiz!
But...!
Ama...
Okiku, once you see my heroics, you might fall for me over that perverted samurai!
kahramanlıklarımı görünce o sapık samurayı boşverip bana gönlünü kaptırabilirsin!
Oh, no, Sir Sanji! I believe you've got the wrong idea!
Hayır, hayır, Sanji-dono, yanlış anlamışsın.
I have a wife and Okiku is my comrade, so that is the extent of our relationship...
Benim karım var ve Okiku sadece yoldaşım, yani öyle bir ilişkimiz yok.
Otsuru is doing well, by the way.
Otsuru-san iyiydi.
You saw her?!
Onu gördün mü?
I did, and she didn't recognize me.
Evet, fark edilmeden.
Is that so...?
Anlıyorum.
I'm glad she's okay...
Durumu iyiyse, güzel o zaman.
but I must refrain from seeing her until we accomplish our great task.
Büyük hedefimizi gerçekleştirene kadar onu göremem.
Sir Kin...
Kin-sama...
Married men shouldn't be popular with the ladies! It's not fair!
Hey, sen evli bir adamsın. Onun kalbini kazanma! Adil değil!
Okiku, please dote on me, too!
Okiku-chan! Lütfen bana karşı nazik ol.
Just shut up...
Kapat çeneni.
Sanji, Kiku is unbelievably strong!
Sanji, Kiku inanılmaz derecede güçlü!
She's not just lovely but also strong?
Güzel olduğu kadar güçlü demek ha?
How perfect.
Kusursuz.
Now, I drew a symbol that implies the date and rendezvous point for our battle.
Evet, savaşın tarihini ve buluşma yerini belirten bir sembol çizdim.
Two birds ablaze...
Engereğin üzerinde...
over a pit viper or a habu...
yanan iki kuş...
and a reversed crescent moon to signify rebellion!
ve isyan anlamına gelen ters hilal!
The day of the Fire Festival. At twilight. The second hour of the bird.
"Ateş Festivali günü. Akşam alacasında. Kuşun ikinci saati.
At Habu Port."
Habu Limanında."
Overseas, "The second hour of the bird" means 5:30 or 6:00 in the evening.
"Kuşun ikinci saati" Wano'da 17:30 - 18:00 saatleri demektir.
Do not worry. The people of Wano will understand.
Endişelenmeyin. Wano halkı mesajı anlayacaktır.
We must distribute these flyers to those who bear the mark of the moon on their left ankles!
Hemen etrafta dolaşıp sol ayak bileklerinde ay işareti olanlara bu kâğıtları vermeliyiz!
The symbol indicates their desire to rebel.
Ay işareti, isyanın sembolüdür.
They are our allies!
Onlar müttefiklerimizdir!
They could be anywhere in Wano...
Wano'da nerede olduklarını bilmiyoruz.
so in order to reach as many people as possible,
Ancak mümkün olduğu kadar çok kişiye dağıtmak için...
we have positioned our friends throughout the country.
arkadaşlarımız tüm ülkeye yayıldı.
Sir Zorojuro and Sir Usohachi are already carrying out this task in the capital.
Zorojuro-dono ve Usohachi-dono da bu görevi başkentte yürütüyorlar.
Ah, I don't think Zoro is helping...
Zoro'nun hiç yardımcı olmadığına eminim.
Furthermore, so that we don't lose our way after arriving at Onigashima,
Dahası, Onigashima'ya vardıktan sonra kaybolmamak için...
we are trying to obtain the blueprints of Kaido's mansion from the carpenter who designed it.
Kaido'nun konağının tasarımını yapan marangozdan planları almaya çalışıyoruz.
So we procured employment for Sir Franosuke under him.
Bu yüzden Franosuke-dono'yu bu işe atadık.
As for Madam Orobi, since we need to know every move Orochi's forces make,
Orobi-dono'ya gelince, Orochi'nin ordusunun tüm hamlelerini öğrenmemiz şart.
I asked her to pose as a geisha in order to secure an audience with Orochi!
Bu yüzden Orochi'nin yanına sızabilmek için geyşa kılığına girmesini istedim!
I heard she has become very popular.
Şu anda çok ünlü olduğunu duydum.
I wanna see Robin in her geisha outfit!
Robin-chan'ı geyşa kıyafetiyle görmek istiyorum!
And now, I would like to delegate tasks to the rest of you.
Şimdi size de görevler vermek istiyorum.
Sir Brook's ability can help us procure food supplies in the capital.
Brook-dono'nun yeteneği, başkentte yiyecek almayı sağlayacaktır.
What...? It can?
He? Emin misin?
Madam Nami's manipulation of the weather is like ninjutsu, so she'll pose as a kunoichi!
Nami-dono'nun hava yetenekleri ninjutsudan farksız, bu sebeple kunoichi rolü yapacak!
That's a female ninja, right?!
Kadın ninja he?
The kunoichi Onami!
Kunoichi Onami!
Nami... A kunoichi?!
Nami-san, kunoichi mi?
Sir Sanji's cooking will be able to gather people together, helping us find recruits.
Sanji-dono'nun aşçılığı kalabalığı çekecek, biz de aralarından gönüllüler bulacağız.
Sir Sanji?
Sanji-dono?
Yeah, leave it to me!
Bana bırak!
What about me?
Peki ya ben?
Madam Carrot and Sir Chopper, I want you to go with Kiku and assist Inuarashi.
Carrot-dono'nun ve Chopper-dono'nun, Kiku'yla birlikte Inuarashi'yle görüşmesini istiyorum.
Kin'emon! I wanna be a ninja, too!
Kin'emon! Ben de ninja olmak istiyorum!
So shall it be!
Tamamdır!
I will provide clothes that are suited to your roles!
Her birinize uygun kıyafetler vereceğim!
Now, put a leaf on your head and brace yourselves!
Bu yüzden kafanıza bir yaprak koyun ve hazır olun!
Are you ready?!
Hazır mısınız?
Here it goes!
Başlıyorum!
My special magical ability!
İşte büyülü gücüm!
Garb-Garb Technique!
Kıyafet Tekniği!
Poof!
Puf!
Nami my sweet!
Nami-swaan!
Ninja!
Ninja!
Since you're wearing appropriate Wanese clothing, it's time to set about your tasks.
Wano tarzı kıyafetler giydiğinize göre görevlerinizi yapmanızı istiyorum.
Wait, Kin'emon!
Bekle, Kin'emon!
Is this really how a kunoichi dresses?!
Bu gerçekten kunoichi kıyafeti mi?
That's how a kunoichi...
Kunoichi dediğin...
should dress!
böyle görünmelidir!
Are you kidding me?!
Yalan söylüyorsun değil mi?
Now then, allow me to summon your guide.
Şimdi, bir rehber çağıracağım.
She is a real kunoichi.
O gerçek bir kunoichi'dir.
A real kunoichi!
Gerçek kunoichi!
Now this is a treat!
İşte büyük zevk!
Shinobu!
Shinobu!
What?!
Ne?
Did you call?!
Beni mi çağırdın?
How they should dress?!
Bu tamamen yanlış!
– What?!
– Ne?!
I won't...
Umudumu...
lose hope...
kaybetmeyeceğim.
Oh no! He's going into shock!
Olamaz! Şokun etkisiyle titriyor!
Kin'emon! Is this just your taste?
Kin'emon! Ağzının tadı bu he?
Kunoichi are either sexy or frumpy. Indeed, there are only two types...
Kunoichi'ler seksi veya demode olmalıdır. İki türleri vardır.
Maybe if I tighten it up...
Sıkıştırırsam iş görür aslında.
Brook, what are you disguised as?
Brook, sen ne kılığına girdin?
A person who wears panties on his head.
Kafasına külot giyen birine.
Or so I thought!
Öyle sanıyordum ama yanılmışım!
Isn't it nice...
Genç olmak...
to be young?
hiç kötü değil.
My name is Shinobu!
Adım Shinobu!
I used to be like a younger sister to Master Kin.
Eskiden Kin-sama'yla kardeş gibiydik.
But now...
Ama şu anda...
I'm known for my Seduction Technique.
imza hareketim, Baştan Çıkarma Tekniği'dir.
Nice to meet you.
Memnun oldum.
If it weren't for Nami, my spirit would've been broken...
Nami-san olmasaydı ruhum yok olurdu.
No, Sanji!
Hayır, Sanji!
I understand, young man...
Anlıyorum, genç adam.
Mature women...
Olgun kadınlar...
are like deadly weapons...
ölümcül silah gibidirler.
All right!
Tamamdır!
Until the rendezvous, we will split up...
Buluşma süresine kadar ayrı kalacağız ama...
but there are three samurai in particular we need to find!
aramanızı istediğim üç özel samuray var!
If we can recruit them, they will be an added boon!
Onları bulabilirsek büyük yardımları dokunacaktır!
Kawamatsu.
Kawamatsu.
Ashura Doji.
Ashura Doji.
Denjiro.
Denjiro.
Like us, those three served as retainers to Lord Oden!
Onlar da bizim gibi Oden-sama'ya hizmet eden samuraylardı!
Let's do this! All of our allies are in place!
Gidelim! Buradaki müttefiklerimiz!
Our targets are Emperor Kaido and the hateful Shogun Kurozumi Orochi!
Hedeflerimiz, Yonko Kaido ve iğrenç şogun Kurozumi Orochi!
We act two weeks from now, on the night of the Fire Festival!
Hareket tarihi iki hafta sonra! Ateş Festivali gecesinde!
We will raid...
Kaido'nun yaşadığı Onigashima'ya...
Kaido's home, Onigashima!
baskın yapacağız!
– What?!
– Ne?!
Hello there!
Selamlar!
Do it!
İşe koyulun!
These fools have the good stuff!
Dangalakların elinde iyi mallar var!
Give that back! Luffytaro gave...!
Geri verin! Onları Luffytaro-san...
Luffytaro gave it to us!
Luffytaro-san bize verdi!
Shut up!
Kes be!
Mother!
Anneciğim!
Oh? There's even fruit, sake, and rice! The nerve...
Ha? Meyveden tut, sake'yle pirince kadar var! Utanmazlara bak hele!
Give that back! It's for my grandson!
Geri verin lütfen! Torunuma yedireceğim!
Shut up, old man! Hurry up and kick the bucket already–
Kafa sikme dayı! Geber git artık!
Who the hell...
Böyle bir şeyi...
pulled a stunt like this?!
hangi sıçtığım yaptı?
Giving people food and acting like a hero?!
İnsanlara yemek verip kahramanlığa soyunmak mı?
It's nothing but a pipe dream for you people.
Hayaliniz kısa sürdü ama...
You may have finally gotten some food...
tam yemek bulmuşken...
but we're taking it; that's how it's gonna be!
bize kaptırıp yine aç kalacaksınız.
There are no samurai left to the poor folk!
Sizin gibi acizleri koruyacak bir samuray kalmadı!
No one left in this country is man enough...
Bu ülkede çetin samuraylara önderlik edebilecek...
to lead our powerful samurai.
adam gibi bir adam da yok artık!
Wano is finished!
Wano'nun sonu geldi!
Got that, you old hag?
Bak hele kocakarı...
Even if you somehow cling to life, nothing will change this cruel reality.
Daha yıllarca yaşasan da acı gerçekten başka bir bok görmeyeceksin.
Let me put you out of your misery!
Gel de sefaletine son vereyim!
Please run!
Lütfen kaç!
Grandma!
Nine!
I believe in Lady Otoki's words...
Otoki-sama'nın sözüne inanıyorum.
She's dead!
Geberdi gitti.
I know that the nine samurai...
Dokuz samurayın...
will fulfill Lord Oden's wish!
Oden-sama'nın arzusunu yerine getireceğinden şüphem yok!
Ridiculous!
Beyinsiz!
A war cannot be fought without a leader!
Başlarında bir önder olmadan savaşa giremezler!
Boss Shutenmaru! That's...!
Shutenmaru-sama! O...
I finally get to meet...
Nihayet karşılaşabildik...
the head of the thieves brigade.
hırsızların lideri.
A-A-A-A monster!
C-C-C-Canavar!
A pirate named Straw Hat Luffy should have come through here...
Buralara Hasır Şapka Luffy isminde bir korsanın gelmiş olması lazım.
I don't suppose your demeanor will change if I tell you I don't know the guy?
"Haberim yok." desem davranışına çekidüzen verir misin?
Don't push your luck.
Kaşınma derim.
Huh?!
Ha?!
The only reason we let you live...
Seni sağ bırakmamızın tek sebebi...
is because Kaido wants you as a subordinate.
Kaido-san'ın seni mürettebata katmak istemesidir.
It doesn't mean I have to show you respect!
Sana saygı göstermeme lüzum yok!
Then, I'll give you my answer...
Öyleyse hemen söyleyeyim.
to that invitation!
İsteğinize yanıtım budur!
Hey, Kin'emon, I understand your plan.
Baksana Kin'emon, planını anladım da...
But there's still one thing that doesn't make sense.
idrak edemediğim bir husus var.
You said that Oden defeated Ashura Doji over twenty years ago...
20 yıl evvel, Oden'in Ashura Doji'yi yendiğini söylemiştin.
So why is he among the allies you want us to find?
Öyleyse bulmamızı istediğin müttefikler arasında ne arıyor?
That's a fair question.
Yerinde bir soru.
Ashura Doji mended his ways after Lord Oden defeated him.
Ashura Doji, Oden-sama'ya yenilince kendini düzelterek...
Indeed, he pledged his loyalty to him.
efendimize bağlılık yemini etti.
However...
Fakat...
We heard he became the head of the Mount Atama Thieves under the name Shutenmaru...
Şimdilerde Atama Dağı Hırsızları lideri olarak Shutenmaru ismiyle...
and has returned to a life of crime.
yine eski günlere döndüğünü işittik.
Hmm, thieves, huh?
Hadi ya, hırsızlar demek?
So then...
Bu arada,
is he strong?
güçlü biri midir?
Yes, and it wouldn't be too much of a stretch to say he might be the strongest samurai.
Evet, muhtemelen en güçlü samuray olduğunu söylemek yanlış olmaz.
I see!
Bak sen!
Don't mess with a samurai!
Bir samurayı küçümsemeyeceksin!
Master Jack!
Jack-sama!
Damn you...
Ağzına sıçtığımın...
Get back! Shutenmaru and Master Jack...
Geri çekilin! Shutenmaru ile Jack-sama...
...are starting to fight!
Birbirine girdiler!
We're doomed!
Sonumuz geldi!
Ever since he died...
O adam, aramızdan ayrıldığından beri...
I've been looking for a way to join him in death.
ölmek için bahane arıyordum.
However...
Fakat...
My death won't come by a flunky like you!
senin gibi bir ayakçının elinden olmaz!
Cut the crap!
Zevzeklik etme!
I...
Ben...
should have died back then!
o gün ölmeliydim!
Living is such a pain.
Yaşamak tam bir işkence.
Master Jack!
J-Jack-sama!
L-Look... The sky!
B-Bakın... Gökyüzü!
No way... Why?
Olamaz! Neden ama?
Why did he come in person?
Hangi amaçla teşrif ediyor ki?
I-Is it because of me? Is it?
B-Benim yüzümden mi? Ondan mı?
Did he come to execute me?!
İnfazım için mi geliyor?
Why, all of a sudden...?
Birden ne oldu böyle?
Is it gonna rain?
Yağmur mu geliyor?
No!
Hayır!
Hey, Straw Hat! Get over here now!
Hey, Hasır Şapka-ya! Çabuk gel!
What's wrong, Traffy?
Ne oldu, Trao?
What the...?
N'oluyor?
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
What?! Lord Momonosuke can turn into a...
Ne? Momonosuke-sama...
...d-dragon?!
E-Ejderha mı oldu?
I will explain later, but yes, he is able to morph into this!
Sonra izah edeceğim, vücudu böyle dönüşebiliyor artık!
Of all things...
Hem de gide gide...
it had to be the form of a damn dragon!
iğrenç bir ejderha şekline giriyor!
We're in trouble, Straw Hat.
Başımız belada, Hasır Şapka-ya.
Move! Outta the way!
Çekil! Önümden çekil!
I don't believe it...
Yok daha neler!
Why...?
Ama neden?
Hey, Jack.
Bak hele Jack.
Yes, sir...
Emredin.
Bring those brats...
Derhâl o veletleri...
to me at once.
huzuruma getir.
Is that... a dragon?!
Ejderha mı? O da ne öyle?
Things can't get any worse...
Daha beteri olamazdı.
That's...
O şey...
Kaido!
Kaido!
So that's...
Demek o...
So Kaido is a dragon?!
Kaido bir ejderha mıymış?
Yes...
Evet.
What you see before you is Kaido!
Gördüğünüz şey, Kaido'dur!
He is able...
Kaido...
to transform into a dragon!
ejderhaya dönüşebiliyor!
Okobore Town is over there!
Okobore Kasabası orada!
But why would Kaido come to Kuri all of a sudden?
Evet. İyi de Kaido durduk yere niye Kuri'ye geldi ki?
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
Affet, Kin'emon.
The truth is they identified me, Straw Hat, and Zoro.
Doğrusu Hasır Şapka-ya, Zoro-ya ile ben, kendimizi ele verdik.
What?!
Ne?!
But that's all they know! Our plan is still under wraps!
Ama hepsi bundan ibaret, planımız açığa çıkmadı.
"That's all they know"?!
Bundan ibaretmiş!
How the hell could you be so sloppy, Law?!
Ne halt yiyorsun lan Law?
You Straw Hat Pirates don't have any right to blame me!
Hasır Şapkalar ağzını hiç açmasın!
Oh, I'm sure it was Luffy's fault.
Ha, kesin Luffy'nin halt yemesidir.
Well, we're sorry.
Üzgün olduğumuzu bil yeter!
He's probably looking for...
Büyük ihtimalle...
me and Straw Hat.
benimle Hasır Şapka-ya'yı arıyor.
Kaido's Beast Pirates maintain...
Kaido'nun emri altındaki Canavar Korsanları'nın...
their overwhelming power thanks to two key factors.
sahip olduğu emsalsiz kuvvetin iki temel dayanağı var.
First, the weapons that Kaido is manufacturing in this country!
İlki, Kaido'nun bu ülke halkına imal ettirdiği silahlar!
Second, the underground trade of Caesar and Doflamingo's manufactured SMILE devil fruits.
Diğeri ise, Doflamingo ve Caesar'ın ürettiği GÜLÜCÜK şeytan meyvelerinin yeraltı ticareti.
We destroyed the source of that trade with the factory on Punk Hazard...
Onun da yuvası olan Punk Hazard'daki fabrikayı yok edip...
and captured Caesar who was necessary for SMILE development.
GÜLÜCÜK tedariki için elzem olan Caesar'ı esir aldık.
On top of that...
Ayrıca,
we destroyed another factory in Dressrosa...
Kaido'nun önemli bir ticaret ortağı...
where Doflamingo, Kaido's critical trading partner, ruled.
Doflamingo'nun işlettiği Dressrosa'daki fabrikayı da yok ettik.
We also were key to the buyer Doflamingo's arrest, bringing him to ruin...
Gedikli müşterisi Doflamingo'ya hapsi boylatarak fişini çektik.
In short...
Özetle,
we picked a fight with Kaido.
savaşın kıvılcımını biz çaktık.
So the only ones he's coming after are...
Peşinde olduğu, başından beri...
me and Straw Hat!
benimle Hasır Şapka-ya'nın kellesidir!
Hey, Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy, wait!
Luffy, bekle!
Sir Luffy!
Luffy-dono!
Don't follow him! I'll go!
Kıpırdamayın! Ben giderim!
If more of us get exposed,
Birkaçımız daha açığa çıkarsa...
they'll find out that all of the Straw Hat and Heart Pirates are here!
Hasır Şapkalar'la Kalp Korsanları mürettebatının tümünün geldiğini anlarlar!
It would kick off a giant manhunt!
Topyekûn peşimize düşerler!
We need to think rationally.
O yüzden kafayı kullanalım.
We're the only ones they've seen.
Bizden başkasını görmediler.
Your plan is still safe!
Planınız hâlâ güvende.
All right?
Anlaştık mı?
Then, what are you two going to do?!
Peki siz ne yapacaksınız?
I wish I could let things be...
Hiç karışmamayı yeğlerdim ama...
but Straw Hat has already gotten involved with the people of this country.
Hasır Şapka-ya halkla içli dışlı oldu bile.
If his emotions take charge, then our plan is doomed.
Duygularına yenik düşerse bir çuval incir berbat olur.
This alliance will have been pointless if we aren't all there on the day of execution.
Büyük günde hep birlikte olmayacaksak ittifakın da bir anlamı kalmaz.
I'll take care of it.
Çaresine bakacağım.
Room!
Oda!
No matter what, do not reveal yourselves!
Ne pahasına olursa olsun kendinizi ele vermeyin!
Shambles!
Değişim!
Captain!
Kaptan!
Damn it, Luffy! What did you do while we were separated?
Ulan Luffy... Biz yokken ne haltlar yedi ki?
Retreat to the forest, Mount Atama Thieves!
Ormana çekilin, Atama Dağı Hırsızları!
We do not want to get involved with him!
Ona bulaşmak istemiyoruz!
I heard rumors...
Kuri'nin dağlarında...
about the mighty brigand living deep in the mountains of Kuri.
kudretli bir hırsız olduğunu işitip duruyorum.
Shutenmaru.
Shutenmaru.
I...
Seni...
remember you...
hatırlıyorum.
But let's not dwell on the past!
Ama geçmişe mazi derler!
If you bend the knee to me...
Emrim altına girersen...
it'll all be water under the bridge.
geçmişe sünger çekeriz!
Whoa! Smells like alcohol!
Öh! Leş gibi alkol kokuyor!
Kaido, don't tell me you're drunk!
Yoksa sarhoş musun, Kaido-san?!
You idiot! I'm not drunk!
Dangalak! Ben sarhoş olmam!
– He's drunk!
– Körkütük sarhoş!
What'll it be, Shutenmaru?
N'apacaksın, Shutenmaru?
We can't get away! We'll have to fight him!
Araya mesafe koyamıyoruz! Kapışsak mı acaba?
Master Jack, I'm trying to stop the bleeding, so don't move!
Jack-sama! Kanamayı durdurmaya çalışırken kımıldamayın!
He's so wasted... He could lose his temper at any moment.
Bu kadar sarhoşken her an gözü dönebilir.
We'd better get out of here.
Biz de uzaklaşsak iyi olur.
Right. But...
Orası öyle de...
the residents of Okobore Town are valuable laborers for our factories!
Okobore Kasabası halkı, fabrikalardaki iş gücünün önemli bir kısmını oluşturuyor!
I'm all for setting an example...
İbretlik oluşturmak tamam da...
but if he wreaks havoc senselessly...
bilinçsizce yakıp yıkarsa geriye ne onlardan...
he'll wipe out all of Kuri.
ne de Kuri'den eser kalır.
Why didn't you tell me sooner, Kiku?!
Neden daha önce söylemedin, Kiku?
Apologies, Sir Kin!
Af buyur, Kin-sama!
Why don't you go back?! I will save Tsuru!
Geri dönsene, Tsuru'yu ben kurtarırım!
No, I share in the responsibility!
Olmaz, benim de bir sorumluluğum var!
I cannot believe she did not get remarried to someone who would protect her!
Kendisine kol kanat gerecek biriyle evlenmediğine inanamıyorum!
It has already been twenty years since I left her!
Ondan ayrıldığımdan bu yana 20 yıl geçti!
I am on my way, Tsuru!
Hemen geliyorum, Tsuru!
Damn! It's still so far away!
Sıçayım! Hâlâ çok mesafe var!
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-ya!
Traffy! You think the people of Okobore Town are okay?!
Trao! Okobore Kasabası sakinleri zarar görmüş müdür sence?
Moron! Now do you see? This is what happens...
Beyinsiz! Görüyor musun işte? Korsanlar iyilik yaparsa...
when pirates do good deeds!
olacağı bu!
Kaido is just after us, right?!
Kaido bizi istiyor, değil mi?
Yeah!
Evet!
Viceroy Kaido!
Başkomutan Kaido!
Isn't he...
O adam...
a headliner?
bir öncü değil mi?
Viceroy! If you're looking for Straw Hat Luffy and Trafalgar Law...
Başkomutan'ım! Hasır Şapka Luffy'yle Trafalgar Law'u arıyorsanız...
they're hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle!
Oden Kalesi'nin kalıntılarında saklanıyorlar.
Oden Castle?
Oden Kalesi mi?
Hawkins!
Hawkins!
That's where Straw Hat and Law are hiding?! Is this the truth?!
Hasır Şapka'yla Law'un Oden Kalesi'nde saklandığı doğru mu?
No... I lied to him to contain his rampage.
Hayır, Başkomutan Kaido'nun sinirini yatıştırmak için yalan söyledim.
But that's not all.
Dahası da var ama.
Maybe it's because of that particular legend, but lately...
Belki de malum efsaneden dolayı şu günlerde...
people are saying that they've seen suspicious lights on the mountain top.
dağın zirvesinde şüpheli ışıklar gördüğünü söyleyenler var.
Legend?
Efsane mi?
Do you mean the one from twenty years ago,
20 yıl evvel katledilen...
where the Kozuki samurai return to enact their revenge, even though we killed them?
Kozuki samuraylarının intikam için döneceğini anlatan efsane mi?
Yes.
Evet.
Instead of letting it incite Shogun Orochi's terror,
Şogun Orochi'nin korkmasına göz yummaktansa...
We can kill two birds with one stone by letting him wipe out that abandoned castle.
terk edilmiş kaleyi yok ederek bir taşla iki kuş vurabiliriz.
Oden Castle, you say?!
Oden Kalesi mi dedin?
That brings back memories... It is indeed a good place to hide.
Anılarım depreşti bak! Cidden iyi bir in.
So that's where they are...!
Demek oradaydılar.
They robbed me of my SMILE production.
GÜLÜCÜK'ü elimden aldılar!
Those damn punks!
Ağzına sıçtığımın yeni yetmeleri!
I won't let them get away!
Elimden kaçırmayacağım!
He's heading toward the ruins of Oden Castle!
Oden Kalesi'nin kalıntılarına gidiyor!
Oh?
Ha?
Hey! Isn't he coming toward us?!
Lan! Üzerimize doğru gelmiyor mu?
– No way!
– Mümkün değil!
Don't tell me he's noticed us!
Yoksa bizi mi fark etti?
– What?!
– Ne?
It can't be!
Olamaz!
It's impossible to see us from there!
O mesafeden fark etmesi imkânsız.
No...
Hayır.
He's coming!
Üzerimize geliyor.
Run for it, guys!
Kaçın millet!
Why is he going over there?!
Kaido neden oraya gidiyor ki?
Impossible...!
Yoksa...
Oh no! That's...!
Olamaz! Bu...
Everyone, run!
Herkes kaçsın!
Blast Breath!
Sıcak Nefes!
– Captain!
– Kaptan!
Kaido!
Kaido!
Shinobu A Veteran Kunoichi
Shinobu Kıdemli Kunoichi
Okobore Town
Okobore Kasabası
"Heaven"
"Cennet"
Boss Shutenmaru Mount Atama Thieves
Shutenmaru Atama Dağı Hırsızları Lideri
"Sake"
"Sake"
Jack Superstar, Beast Pirates
Jack Önder, Canavar Korsanları
"Law & Straw Hat Form Pirate Alliance"
"Law ile Hasır Şapka Korsan İttifakı"